Another one of the same.
Here alone? What do you say,
want to come with me after this?
Thank you.
That was cold!
You didn't have to ignore me.
Don't involve yourself with me.
See? I told you.
I've had enough!
I clean and clean, but you
just make it total chaos again!
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm telling you to clean up after
yourself when you're done eating!
Okay, sure. Check in again tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yep. Tomorrow, they'll
mysteriously be cleaned up.
Huh?
That's because I clean them up!
That's another way of putting it.
Sheesh!
--Hurry up and clean, already!
--Ow.
Okay, fine!
Jeez... This is one of those "Your parents
must be really something" situations.
I don't...
I don't have any parents.
No, that's not what I meant by that...
Hey, you... Ow!
Hey... No, wait!
Dante, you jerk! Well, forget you!
Hey, is Pat...
Made her mad again, huh?
Shut up.
What do you want? If you're going to
clean up for me, you're very welcome.
You want someone to do that, hire a maid.
You can use the pay from this job.
I'd like you to hold on to this for a while.
Isn't this a job for the coin
lockers at the train station, Morrison?
Come on, don't be so hasty.
See, this is a historic
heirloom that's been passed down
in Miss Nina's family for generations.
This pendant is priceless.
She says that she inherited it when her old
man died, but that in the ten years since then,
those who want it are out for her
blood whenever they smell a chance.
Ten years... Why do you suddenly want
to give it to someone after that long?
Well, the attacks weren't
so frequent up until now,
but lately she's targeted all the time,
and she's frequently been in danger.
So, it's time for you to step in.
Would you take this on for me?
I don't want to hear any
stupid answers, partner.
Sure, all right. I was at loose ends anyway.
I'll take on the job for you.
That jerk Dante.
He just has no delicacy!
Jeez, he doesn't have any parents either...
Hi, Dante!
Oh, you're alone today?
I'm always alone, you know that.
Now, now, girls that age
get hurt real easily.
Hurry up and apologize to
Shortie, and make friends again.
Heh, it's none of your business.
You hurry up and bring me the usual.
Okay!
Sheesh...
Dante, you jerk!
Why the long face?
If you've got the time to sit here grumbling
into your sundae dish, go do some work.
You still haven't paid back
all you owe me, you know.
I'm doing work now.
What's this?
A pendant.
I can see that! I'm asking you,
what's with this pendant?
I'm its bodyguard...
No, necklace-guard, I guess.
That wasn't funny.
Thanks for waiting!
Mom...
Huh, can it really be that valua...
What's with you?
This one thing I can't let you
turn into payment on the debt.
As if I'd take it! It's not yours.
--Got it!
--Hey!
Even I'm not that evil, you know.
Well, work hard and pay me back soon.
This just isn't right.
It's too late to say that.
You've already handed it over to him.
We just have to watch over
him and see what happens.
I did what you told me because
you said he could handle it, but...
I didn't want to let you
face any more danger.
And it's true that he's a man we can trust.
If I just carry that pendant, I have
the power to defeat lower-level ones.
I know that.
But there's no guarantee that
your attackers will always be small fry.
True, but...
It looks like it's begun.
Who the hell are you?
Where did the woman go?
Do you have the magic stone now?
By "magic stone," do you mean this?
Wait! What are you even going
to do if you go out there now?
Please, let me go.
Nina!
If I just get that magic stone,
I'll have the power of my master.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but anyway, it's time to go to sleep now.
Bye.
Man, I thought I'd be able to
have a little more fun there.
My, my. If you came to cheer me on, too bad.
Things just ended.
Pretty wicked, aren't you?
After all, you kept quiet about the fact
that the ones after the necklace were devils.
You defeated the devil?
This type of thing is my specialty, you see.
So, who's that?
An old friend.
I'm Simon.
Simon's the one who told me about you.
He told me there was an odd-jobs
man who would even protect
a demon-summoning pendant.
But please give it back.
I just can't let strangers be
put in danger because of me!
Then will you give me my pay
for the work I've done up 'til now?
Yes, I'll pay you tomorrow.
Then tomorrow is when I'll return this, too.
All right. I'll come to your office tomorrow.
Wait, Mom!
Mom!
Patty?
Mom. Mo...
Mom!
Mom...
Come on, I'll drive you home.
Come to the office tomorrow
like you always do.
That woman you think is your mother
is supposed to show up with my pay.
I know she's my mother!
So you think you can take
care of me any time, eh?
Your conceit will be the death of you, Dante.
Come on, Patty, cheer up already and clean...
Whatever, never mind.
Man, she's really late, isn't she?
She'd better really be trustworthy, Morrison.
What are you saying?
You trusted her enough to
tell her to bring your pay here.
That's not what I mean.
You're wondering whether
she might be a demon herself?
Sure, she didn't tell me the crew out
for her necklace were demons either,
but she herself seemed
like a normal human to me.
And she's renting a hotel room here
in the human world, all normal-like.
What hotel?
The Grandia Hotel, if memory serves.
Sheesh...
Please, don't make this place
any more of a mess than it is.
You're not one to talk, Dante!
Hey!
What's with Patty?
I thought she wanted to see Nina.
Beats me. She probably remembered
some TV show she wanted to watch.
She's a hopeless brat.
Phone, Dante.
Jeez, what a pain.
Devil May Cry.
Oh, it's you?
What? Are you sure about that?
Of course. I came all the way out
to the public library to confirm it.
If you need them, I'll collect
the references for you, too.
Yeah, good idea. Thanks, I'm counting on you.
Was that Nina?
Nope. More than about Nina,
it was about this necklace's...
Hey, Morrison, what did
you do with the pendant?
Huh?!
Mom...
Patty...
Simon! Come in.
Thanks.
Perfect timing. I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
I'd like you to go to that
odd-job man's place now
and get back the pendant
in exchange for this pay.
You can just go yourself.
I don't want to go.
Because that "Patty" girl
might be there, perhaps?
I can't be with her. You should know that.
Yes... Yes, you're right.
Oh, did you do something to your hand?
Nothing really, I just spilled
some coffee this morning.
But I thought you couldn't stand coffee...
Oh, was that right?
You...
That's strange. I can't
imagine the book is that popular.
My, this is a surprise. Do devils study too?
Unlike Dante, I have an
avid thirst for knowledge.
--By the way, that book...
--Huh?
What the heck is the deal?
Never mind, just drive faster.
You got it.
Are you awake?
Who are you?
--A good question.
--What do you want?
What do I want? You should
know that better than anyone else.
But it only means anything to demons...
Are you a demon?
But if you are,
the pendant should react to you...
True, that stone reacts
to the powers of demons.
But when the demon's power is just too
weak, it doesn't have much of an effect.
My powers are extremely weak.
I'm a demon with no power.
As you can see, to take human form,
I have to actually wear human skin!
Then, Simon is...
Sorry, but I threw away the insides.
That's how it is, Nina Lowell.
Now if I get the final part, your necklace,
I'll have everything I need.
About the guest that's reserved the suite...
Hey!
I'm telling you, we can't give out
information about guests. It's the policy of--
Would you rather break hotel policy,
or have a big hole open up in your face?
Now, I guess it's about
time to go pick them up.
Pick them up?
Don't play dumb with me. I know.
That necklace, and your daughter...
I need both together, or I can't
complete the ceremony, right?
Please, just leave Patty out of this.
"Leave her out of this," huh?
Yeah, you would want that.
After all, that's why you had to
part ways with your own daughter.
Patty!
You really are my mother?
Patty, run away!
You really are my mother, aren't you.
Patty, never mind, just run!
This is a happy surprise.
I never imagined you'd bring
that to me of your own free will.
I guess that means luck
has finally turned my way.
All right, take the necklace and
go stand in front of that altar.
Patty, you mustn't listen to what this man...
Mom!
You keep your mouth shut!
Now, hurry up. Otherwise...
No, Pat--
Get a move on!
Yes, there is fine.
Now all you have to do is place that
necklace on the center of the altar.
Hurry!
Patty, stop!
Okay, is this what you wanted?
Will you let Mom go, then?
Sure, that's fine. Here!
Mom!
It's here! It's here!
Now I can become a king of the demon world
that surpasses even the four great devils!
Mom! Mom...
What have...
What have we done?
Mom?
Dante!
Ack! What the heck is going on?!
Morrison, take these two
and get away from the hotel.
H-Hey!
While you're at it, I suggest chasing
everyone else out of the hotel, too!
As if I can get that many out at once!
Dante!
--What's this?
--What happened?
Whatever, just evacuate everyone, fast!
I can't very well just...
Get your ass in gear!
You can come here,
but you're too late to do anything.
Unfortunately for you,
I've gotten hold of Abigail's legacy.
You're always scurrying around
behind the scenes pulling cheap tricks...
I've gotten really sick of seeing your face.
How about we say our goodbyes?
What, did you think I'd beg
for my life or something?
Fool. I'm different than I was before.
I'll show you.
Everyone hurry!
I'll show you the power of Abigail,
who once rivaled the demon king!
What the heck?
It's over.
The world is ending.
Don't you go dying, Dante.
Everything with a beginning also has an end.
That's the rule.
It may be sad, but looking all gloomy
just because it's the end isn't my thing.
Since it's the end, all the more
reason to paint the town red instead.
If you do that, you can keep
smiling no matter how things pan out.